multiplestreammktg.com 2015-12-26

# Privacy Policy - Multiple Stream Media. Full Service Internet Advertising And Marketing Services.

## Our Privacy Policy

Multiple Stream Media has established this Privacy Policy to explain how it protects and manages the personal information that it collects from you (the customer, subscriber, vendor) online.

**1\. Consent for Collection, Use and Disclosure  
**  
Your use of the Multiple Stream Media site and/or your registration for Multiple Stream Media products and services constitute your consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Multiple Stream Media site.

Multiple Stream Media may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When it does, Multiple Stream Media will also revise the “last update” date at the top of this Privacy Policy. In addition, Multiple Stream Media will seek a customer's prior consent, by email, for any new uses or proposed disclosures of information collected from the customer prior to the change. Multiple Stream Media will notify customers by email of changes to this policy that will affect information collected from them in the future. In certain circumstances, however, Multiple Stream Media will not inform and obtain the consent of the customer, such as in connection with an investigation of a breach of an agreement, contravention of laws, an emergency where the security, life, health of an individual is threatened, the collection of a debt or in compliance with the request of a law enforcement agency or a court order.

A customer may withdraw his or her consent for collection, use and disclosure at any time by sending an email to unsubscribe@multiplestreammktg.com. Please note that, if you do, Multiple Stream Media may suspend its provision of products and services to you. When you unsubscribe, if you fall within the guarantee period for any Multiple Stream Media product and you request a refund, the guarantee will be honored.

**2\. Accountability  
**  
Multiple Stream Media collects, at the time of your registration and your sign-on to its web site, certain “personal information” (information that personally identifies you) including but not limited to your name, email address, home or work address, telephone number, and information about your computer hardware and software (e.g., IP address, operating system, browser type, domain name, URL, access times, and referring web site addresses).

Multiple Stream Media has implemented this Privacy Policy to protect personal information received from its customers, and to respond to any inquiries. The Privacy Policy also provides that Multiple Stream Media will use appropriate contractual means to establish a comparable level of protection for personal information which is sent for processing by third parties on Multiple Stream Media's behalf.

Multiple Stream Media has designated responsibility for your personal information to its Privacy Officer, who ensures compliance with the principles in this Privacy Policy. Other Multiple Stream Media individuals may be delegated to act on behalf of the Privacy Officer.

**3\. Purposes for Collecting Personal Information  
**  
Multiple Stream Media collects and uses personal information for the following Identified Purposes:

(a) to understand customer needs regarding Multiple Stream Media's services;

(b) to develop and provide our web site and our products and services for our customers;

(c) to fulfill your requests for products, services or information;

(d) to communicate with customers and site visitors, when necessary, and to inform customers of upgrades, as well as of other products and services available from Multiple Stream Media, its affiliates and third parties;

(e) to allow customers to access limited-entry areas of Multiple Stream Media's site;

(f) to personalize some of our services and products for you and to deliver targeted advertisements and offers from Multiple Stream Media and third parties;

(g) to bill accounts and maintain payment records;

(h) to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or government request;

(i) to respond to a legitimate claim, or to address our reasonable belief, that you are violating the rights of any third party or any of the agreements or policies that govern your use of the Multiple Stream Media site or any Multiple Stream Media product or service;

(j) to protect the services, products or rights of Multiple Stream Media, including but not limited to the security or integrity of the Multiple Stream Media site; and

(k) to identify and resolve technical problems concerning Multiple Stream Media's site, products and services.

Multiple Stream Media also uses personal information in an aggregate form (i.e., not individually attributable to you) for its business analysis, operational, marketing and other promotional purposes.

If we hire other companies to provide some products or services on our behalf, then we will only provide those companies the personal information they need for the Identified Purposes, and we will limit their rights to use and further disclose your personal information as appropriate in the course of their work for us.

**4\. Limiting the Collection of Personal Information  
**  
Multiple Stream Media limits its collection of personal information to only that information which is necessary for the Identified Purposes. Multiple Stream Media does not direct its site to, nor does it knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of thirteen.

When you visit the Multiple Stream Media web site, a cookie may be placed on your computer or the cookie may be read if you have visited the Multiple Stream Media site previously. Multiple Stream Media uses cookies to allow Multiple Stream Media to determine which products and services you have already purchased so that Multiple Stream Media does not provide redundant information to you, and, if you are an Multiple Stream Media affiliate, to track Multiple Stream Media sales made to customers referred by you so that you can receive compensation under our affiliate program. If you choose to not have your browser accept cookies from the Multiple Stream Media web site, you may not be able to view all the text on the screens, or to experience a personalized visit, or to subscribe to certain service and product offerings on the Multiple Stream Media site.

**5\. Disclosure, Processing and Retention  
**  
Multiple Stream Media does not sell, rent or disclose your personal information to anyone else, except:

(a) to someone you have designated to act as your agent, for one or more of the Identified Purposes (listed in Section 2, above);

(b) to Multiple Stream Media's employees, independent contractors, subsidiaries, affiliates, consultants, business associates, service providers, suppliers and agents, acting on Multiple Stream Media's behalf for any of the Identified Purposes;

(c) as necessary if Multiple Stream Media has reason to believe that disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference (either intentionally or unintentionally) with Multiple Stream Media's rights or property, other users of Multiple Stream Media's web site, products or services, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities; and

(d) to respond to judicial process and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law.

In addition, as we continue to develop our business, we or our affiliates may sell or buy other businesses or entities, or we may merge with another company. In such transactions, personal information may be one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the event that Multiple Stream Media or substantially all of its assets are acquired, your personal information may be one of the transferred assets.

Your information may be stored and processed in the United States, or in any other country in which Multiple Stream Media or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities. By using this web site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.

After your account becomes inactive (that is, if you request to be removed from our database), Multiple Stream Media will keep your personal information in its archives. Your information will then be used only as necessary for tax reasons or to prove Multiple Stream Media's compliance with any applicable law.

**6\. Accuracy of Personal Information  
**  
Multiple Stream Media will use reasonable efforts to keep customer personal information accurate for the Identified Purposes, and for minimizing the possibility of making inappropriate customer decisions based on such information. Customers are responsible for informing Multiple Stream Media about changes to their personal information. You can do this by calling 845-383-1007. Multiple Stream Media will use new or updated personal information it receives from customers to update its own records.

**7\. Security Safeguards  
**  
Multiple Stream Media will use reasonable efforts to protect customers' personal information.

**8\. Access to Personal Information  
**  
Multiple Stream Media will afford you a reasonable opportunity to review the personal information in your file, if you so request by calling 845-383-1007, writing to:

Multiple Stream Media  
544 Sawmill Road  
Hurley, NY 12443

... or upon request to the Privacy Person.

If Multiple Stream Media is not able to provide access to some aspect of a customer's personal information, it will provide reasons for denying access such as; that by doing so would likely reveal personal information about a third party, or that it is confidential commercial information or attorney-client privileged communications, or that the information relates to a breach of an agreement or a contravention of law, or that its disclosure could reasonably be expected to threaten the life or security of another individual.

Customers have the right to request that inaccurate or incomplete information be amended as appropriate, by contacting Multiple Stream Media or the Privacy Officer as described above. Multiple Stream Media will promptly correct such personal information.
